Humans!
If you wish not for
annihilation, take heed!
I bear a message from the depths!
You will surrender the surface
to us, the Clan of the Seafolk!
Thereafter you shall become
our nourishment, human scum—
Nice head! Are you related to
an octopus by any chance?
I heard it was that same guy again.
What was his name?
I forget, but he's super-strong.
HE TAKES EVERY OPPONENT OUT WITH A SINGLE PUNCH.
BUT PEOPLE SAY HE STEALS OTHERS' CREDIT.
I MEAN, HE'S CLASS C.
Class C?
Never seen him before.
I've got to keep up.
THE DEEP SEA KING
Help! Somebody!
We, the Clan of the Seafolk,
now rule the surface!
It is useless to resist!
You'll pay for that, human!
The Class A hero Stinger,
rising in popularity and currently
11th in the rankings, is here to help.
At your service, everyone!
It's Stinger!
We're saved!
Go for it!
Well now...
Anyone who needs a new blowhole
drilled into their torso, step right up!
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
sanjou, hisshou, shijou saikyou
He joins the fight, he wins, the strongest in history
nan datten da, frustration
Are you talking to him? Frustration ☹
ore wa tomaranai
He's not going to stop
one punch, kanryou, rensenrenshou
One punch, that's it, one fight after another
ore wa katsu, tsune ni katsu, asshou
He wins, he always wins, overwhelmingly
power, get power
Power, get power
girigiri genkai made
On to the very edge
Hero
ore o tataeru koe ya
There are voices praising him
kassai nante hoshiku wa nai sa
but he's not doing this for acclaim
Hero
dakara hitoshirezu aku to tatakau
So he just fight evil without end
Nobody knows who he is
sora ooi oshiyoseru teki
Enemies to fight are numerous as the stars
ore wa se wo muke wa shinai
and he's not gonna turn his back on you
Hero
naraba yuruginaki kakugo shita tame
He's made up his mind and ain't gonna yield
tatakau hero
A fighting hero
kodoku na hero
A lone hero
I
i wanna be a saikyou hero
I wanna be the strongest hero
Master...
You have moved up to
rank 2 in Class C.
You are on the verge of
entering Class B!
Class B, huh?
That means I won't have any more
weekly hero quotas, right?
Correct.
Oh, excuse me...
Hello?
City J? It is a bit far.
Are there no
competent heroes nearby?
Busy guy...
Master!
The monster you defeated
on your way home the other day
called itself one of
the “Seafolk,” right?
I forget.
Several monsters calling themselves
the “Clan of the Seafolk”
have appeared in City J and
are attacking anyone in sight.
A Class A hero fighting them
all alone and on the brink of defeat.
His extreme fatigue
and pain are apparent
A prompt response from
the Hero Association
is desperately needed.
Hang on!
The threat level is Tiger.
All citizens are asked to
stay out of the area.
You've got spunk,
you slimy bastards.
My beloved Bamboo Shoot here
is happy to be battling enemies
with some grit for a change.
But it's time to end this.
You can quit your boasting, human!
Your foolish fan club has run off.
But your death will not be easy.
For the taking of our brothers' lives,
long will we cause you to suffer.
Four fish to go!
It's a lot easier
without an audience!
Sing, Bamboo Shoot!
Gigantic Drill Stinger
Quadruple Thrust!
I did it...
I did it!
These monsters were probably
a God-level threat...
and I defeated them all by my—
You know,
when something's so annoying,
it is a pleasure to watch it die.
How much farther is City J?
We are almost there.
But I am getting no readings.
I will scout ahead.
Once I have confirmed their
location, I will let you know.
Oh...hey!
This is an announcement
from the Hero Association.
The threat level is Tiger.
All citizens, please stay clear of the area.
CITY A - HERO ASSOCIATION HQ
Was the warning issued?
The request just went out.
We'll need to update it and re-issue.
What do you mean?
Stinger is down.
Mumen Rider here. I'm heading in.
Give me the location.
All lines are busy at this time—
- Where are they?
- Hey, best forget it!
Class C heroes
can't handle this one.
- Huh?
- The word just came down.
Emergency evacuation warning.
The threat level has been
raised from Tiger to Demon.
All residents of City J,
- See what I mean?
please evacuate immediately.
Hey!
I repeat. All residents of City J,
please evacuate immediately.
Evacuate?
How foolish.
As if I'd allow even one
of these apes to escape.
So that's the one that got Stinger...
But he's the last of ‘em.
Should I wait for backup?
If it's one-on-one, maybe I can—
That smarts.
Why would you do this?
Dammit, how'd he get behind me?
I was so surprised my voice
went all funky.
Plus, my gunpowder-charged
lightning kick had zero effect!
I can't win.
Who are you?
I am...
Lightning Max, the hero...
Fight me.
Fight you? Of course.
I'll run for it as soon as—
What happened?
I can't feel my body...
Dammit.
You arrogant...
Lightning Flying Backwards
Roundhouse Kick!
Class S hero,
Puri-puri Prisoner.
I escaped from prison...
just to see you!
Well, well.
A hero serving time in prison?
I tagged along and
was able to escape too.
My thanks.
Prisoner number 4188, Sonic, right?
Surprised I know?
You see, I check up on all
the boys who catch my eye.
I'm serving a life sentence because
I can't resist attacking beautiful men.
Oh my.
More soldiers come for me?
Goodness!
I feel the strength about
to erupt out of him!
Sonic, dear, you hang back.
Class A rank 11, sweet Stinger.
Class A rank 20, Lighting Max.
I fancied them both.
And yet you ruined them!
Now that Genos has passed me,
I am the lowest in rank...
but I am still Class S!
I am unlike either of them.
I'll begin at half-power,
to gauge how much you can take.
You made me rip the hand-knit
sweater my boyfriend made!
I will never, ever forgive you!
A delectable slab of meat, quite prime.
My appetite's up!
Huh?
Oh my...
I felt that...
just a little.
I felt that too...a little.
Puri-puri Prisoner is acting
tough, but he's hurting...
So this is what a fight between
a demon-level monster
and a Class S hero looks like?
It's almost comical.
Neither one could defeat me.
Dammit... His punch was
stronger than I expected.
But I must not lose to him.
I can't have any more of my
boys destroyed by this monster...
I have no choice.
I'll have to transform.
Ready...
Transform!
Puri-puri Prisoner Angel Style!
He's naked.
And he's definitely no angel.
Nor is he human.
Nor do I want to watch.
I'm out.
No one has ever seen my Angel
Style and lived to tell about it.
All the more reason to leave.
Quite unsightly.
Are those...your last words?
Angel Rush!
Elevated energy levels nearby.
That must be it.
Damn it! I have no way
to reach Master!
It cannot be helped.
Done with your combo?
I felt that...a little.
Hear me.
The objective of a combination
move is to finish your opponent.
Each separate attack must be
delivered with intent to kill.
Like this.
Isn't this fun?
Just who are you?
I am the Deep Sea King.
As lord of the Clan of the Seafolk,
this world is mine to rule.
Do you dare defy me too?
You think you have the strength
to rule the surface all alone?
That's pathetic.
Oh?
Then I suppose you must die.
That's my line.
I would have let you live if you'd
shown me the respect I'm due.
I'm no hero, but I will eliminate you.
The rain...is falling.
Too slow.
Wind Blade Leg!
Deep Sea King, I see
right through your moves.
Are you sure of that?
Once it bites, my little
moray here never lets go!
Let me be clear.
There's no way I'd ever lose to you.
It's useless.
You may have power...
but you're too slow to fight me.
I'm glad, Deep Sea King!
Fighting something like you just
confirms how strong I really am!
You see, my moves are
the fastest and the strongest!
Now what, lost your mind?
He's faster!
Stronger too?!
What happened to him?
He's huge!
The air of the surface
shriveled me up a bit,
but thanks to this rain,
I feel like myself again.
Your attacks don't hurt me...
even a little!
At this time,
the whereabouts of the Seafolk
that attacked City J are unknown.
Several heroes who tried to stop them
have been found
unconscious at the scene
and remain in critical condition.
Of all the times to hit a red light...
Where'd he run off to?
Wait, you're...
Class C, rank 2.
You a hero too?
Have you seen Genos?
Genos?
Today, as our guest, we have
the top-ranked, Class A superhero
who has also been number
one in popularity rankings
for 28 weeks straight.
He's also a successful
model, actor and singer.
Let's welcome the
handsome Mr. Amai Mask!
Thank you for having me.
We are currently facing
a threat level of Demon.
How do you assess the situation?
That is a difficult question.
Why is that?
I'm only a hero when I confront evil.
The rest of the time, I'm
focused on my career as an artist.
I see.
I'm only here today
to promote my new song.
My apologies.
In that case, let's discuss your song.
Let me just say this.
To assuage the public's
fears and worries,
heroes need to be
both tough and strong
so that they can defeat evil
with speed, grace, and brilliance.
I find it regrettable
that there were heroes
who were completely
beaten by evil this time.
So that no hero ever dies in vain,
I hope each will
continue to train his hardest.
My attacks have no effect.
Could I be lacking in power?
I can't kill him unarmed.
I need to retreat for now
and find a weapon.
Caught you!
Crack crack, snap snap.
Huh?
Wait there.
The next time we meet
will be your demise.
No matter.
The small fry can be let go.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
There were orders to evacuate.
A hero?
If you're after the Deep Sea King,
better forget it.
Deep Sea King?
You heroes could all jump
him at once and still lose.
You're fine at playing make-believe,
but against true power
you don't stand a chance.
You can't protect a thing.
Who was that pervert?
The Seafolk?!
I sense numerous
life signals nearby.
With so many...
The evacuation shelter!
Daddy, are the scary
monsters still outside?
Don't worry. As long as
we're in this shelter, we're safe.
Besides...if it comes down to it,
I'm sure all of us together
can beat a monster or two.
I sense them...
Yes, so many!
It's coming from...
over there!
Greetings...
and goodbye.
Please wait!
We surrender!
We will comply with
any demands you have.
But please do not attack. I beg you.
I'm only Class C, so I
evacuated. Now I'm trapped.
I'm no hero. I'm a failure...
Surrender?
I've come to kill you.
Your deaths are inevitable!
And as for my demands...
How about I demand you scream
nicely as I slaughter you?
I can't win...
I know it won't amount to much,
but all I can do is buy time for
the Class S heroes to get here.
But look at this monster...
Who am I kidding?
I can't buy time just
by talking to him.
I pissed my pants...
I'm pathetic.
I'll fight with you!
Heroes?
There are others in here too?
I may be the lowest ranking at 38,
but I'm still a Class A hero.
We can do this.
I-I'm a hero too!
Allback-man is here!
Heroes?
The heroes are here?
Heroes!
They'll save us!
I feel better with a Class A around.
Yeah...
Two Class C's, one
Class B and one Class A...
We can do it!
We can win!
You sure this is the way?
Yes, since residents are
fleeing from this direction,
we'll find monsters further up.
Did you see a butt
naked guy run past?
What?
Maybe he was taking a
bath and was left behind.
I'll check it out.
Go on without me.
Got it!
Mumen Rider here.
Yes, we're on our way.
What! The shelter?
It was the other way!
All right. When I give
the signal, charge him.
One...
Two...
That's weird.
I know I saw him...
Why so quiet all of a sudden?
Are you one of the Seafolk?
Mumen Rider went in?
Yes. I couldn't stop—
Mumen Rider?!
What's your location?
This is beyond you.
The monster even took
out a Class S hero!
We need to assemble
a subjugation squad.
A Class S hero was defeated?
Who is this?
Where's Mumen Rider?
Stand-up Peddling Mode!
Roar, Justice!
Is this the Hero Association?
Yes. Who are you?
Give me the owner of
that cell phone right now!
This is the hero Saitama.
Saitama?
Hey, come back home soon
On nights when the new moon shivers from my sighs
I close my eyes and think of you
I want to see you... I feel like crying
I feel so romantic
I hope these feelings reach you
I know very well
how hard you work all the time
You're the one I love
You're so strong but I'm still worried
Don't hide your weakness, at least show it to me
I'll find you before any stars
Come straight back home
Hey, come back home soon
NEXT
EPISODE
UNYIELDING JUSTICE
Hey, how'd you like my Gigantic Drill Stinger?
By the way, I nailed ten of those Seafolk things!
You're pretty upbeat.
Oh, Lightning Max?
I won't ask how many Seafolk you defeated,
but I'm sure you did great.
Next time on One-Punch Man Episode 9,
“Unyielding Justice.”
I'm not sure who'll mete it out,
but make sure our sacrifices weren't in vain!